import { Question } from "../types";

const questions: Question[] = [
  {
    question: "2 + 2 = ?",
    answers: ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    correctAnswer: "4",
  },
  {
    question: "5 * 3 = ?",
    answers: ["15", "20", "10", "25"],
    correctAnswer: "15",
  },
  {
    question: "10 - 7 = ?",
    answers: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
    correctAnswer: "3",
  },
  {
    question: "8 / 2 = ?",
    answers: ["2", "4", "6", "8"],
    correctAnswer: "4",
  },
  {
    question: "9 + 6 = ?",
    answers: ["14", "15", "16", "17"],
    correctAnswer: "15",
  },
  {
    question: "12 - 4 = ?",
    answers: ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
    correctAnswer: "8",
  },
  {
    question: "7 * 2 = ?",
    answers: ["12", "13", "14", "15"],
    correctAnswer: "14",
  },
  {
    question: "16 / 4 = ?",
    answers: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
    correctAnswer: "4",
  },
  {
    question: "14 + 5 = ?",
    answers: ["18", "19", "20", "21"],
    correctAnswer: "19",
  },
  {
    question: "20 - 8 = ?",
    answers: ["10", "11", "12", "13"],
    correctAnswer: "12",
  },
  {
    question: "6 * 3 = ?",
    answers: ["16", "17", "18", "19"],
    correctAnswer: "18",
  },
  {
    question: "18 / 3 = ?",
    answers: ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
    correctAnswer: "6",
  },
  {
    question: "9 + 10 = ?",
    answers: ["18", "19", "20", "21"],
    correctAnswer: "19",
  },
  {
    question: "15 - 5 = ?",
    answers: ["9", "10", "11", "12"],
    correctAnswer: "10",
  },
  {
    question: "3 * 4 = ?",
    answers: ["10", "11", "12", "13"],
    correctAnswer: "12",
  },
  {
    question: "24 / 6 = ?",
    answers: ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    correctAnswer: "4",
  },
  {
    question: "11 + 7 = ?",
    answers: ["17", "18", "19", "20"],
    correctAnswer: "18",
  },
  {
    question: "13 - 6 = ?",
    answers: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
    correctAnswer: "7",
  },
  {
    question: "5 * 5 = ?",
    answers: ["20", "22", "24", "25"],
    correctAnswer: "25",
  },
  {
    question: "30 / 5 = ?",
    answers: ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
    correctAnswer: "6",
  },
];

export default questions;
